freelinks.com 2013-05-03

# Privacy Policy - Free Links

**Privacy Policy Statement For Free Links**

This is the web site of FREELINKS.COM LLC. 

Our postal address is  
808 N Franklin St 1412  
Tampa, FL 33602

We can be reached via e-mail at freelinksllc@gmail.com. 

For each visitor to our web page, our web server does not automatically recognize any information regarding the visitor's domain or e-mail address. 

We collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations. 

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our web pages. 

**With respect to cookies:** Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

**With respect to Ad Servers:** To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have a relationship with Google that allows them to place ads on our web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, Google may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information when viewing pages that include their advertisements. For further information, consult the privacy policy of Google here: http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html 

**More About Your Personal Information:**

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us an e-mail at the above address. 

If you supply us with your postal address on-line you will only receive the information for which you provided us your address. 

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed on-line. 

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will contact you before we use your data for these new purposes to notify you of the policy change and to provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. 

Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by e-mailing us at the above address. 

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to unique identifier information (e.g., customer number or password) that we maintain about them, communications that the consumer/visitor has directed to our site (e.g., e-mails, customer inquiries), contact information (e.g., name, address, phone number) that we maintain about them . 

Consumers can access this information by e-mailing us at the above address or writing to us at the above address. 

Consumers can have this information corrected by sending us an e-mail at the above address or writing to us at the above address. 

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses.
